<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Analysis Portfolio on Perry Burton</title>
    <link>https://peburton.github.io/Data_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Analysis Portfolio on Perry Burton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://peburton.github.io/Data_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NM Cannabis Sales Data | Google Sheets, Google BigQuery, SQL, Tableau</title>
      <link>https://peburton.github.io/Data_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peburton.github.io/Data_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The inspiration for this analysis comes from my background as a journalist working on the border of Texas and New Mexico.
When the recreational sale of cannabis began on April 1, 2022 I was in the newsroom &amp;ndash; sending out crews, researching dispensaries, and putting together a show for broadcast. Since then &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;ve kept a close eye on the sales figures out of the Land of Enchantment.
TLDR New Mexican cities along the borders with neighboring states tend to have a disproportionate number of sales (largely recreational) compared to similarly sized areas further into the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://peburton.github.io/Data_Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://peburton.github.io/Data_Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Since building my first PC at 14, I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a love for computers and technology. That only grew as I entered adulthood, intitally enrolling in university as a computer science major although it didn&amp;rsquo;t stick for long. I transitioned into the humanities, first as an English major and then transitioning to Journalism. I added Political Science as a second major after taking a political theory course and being amazed at how much there was to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
